sounds like we're gonna put you in a
home soon that's what that sounds like
my parents they're good people though
they're great they're my dad my dad's
count goofy though he makes his own kale
chips yeah that makes his own kale chips
he calls me up all the time he's like
Tom I just made a new batch of kale
chips
you got try these these are chips made
from kale once you have these you're
never gonna want a regular chip ever
again cuz they were so delicious so I
finally tried one I was like oh my dad
forgot what chips tastes like this is
the worst thing I've ever fooling about
kale chips are not good they're
basically like someone left a salad out
for five days
I like those are chips now get him in
your belly
my mom's funny too though she's
interesting shake she's really new agey
like she's into like energy and crystals
and stuff and she's been getting weirder
like I called her a while ago
I was like what are you up to mom and
she was like I'm activating rivers it's
like oh okay so you got a job with the
city or something you you cleaning up
reference and she's like no I get my
crystals out I go the mouth of the river
I do a little ceremony
I put the crystal in and it activates
the river I was like Oh sounds like
we're gonna put you in a home soon
that's what that sounds like what I
think you just been running around town
throwing crystals into rivers you're
gonna get picked up mom we can't be
doing that
you gotta have permits to River activate
but she loves doing it she travels all
over the country she plans these camping
trips by rivers so she can sit like
she's got a website if you ever want to
look up which rivers have been activated
in North America to find out but she has
a lot of fun so after a while I was like
maybe I should learn more about River
activation in case I have to take over
the family business I want to make sure
I'm doing it right so I was like here's
explain this a little more so like when
you put the crystal in the river what
does it do to show you it's been
activated like does it start bubbling or
make a sound or like the ducts get real
happy swimming around it all this feels
amazing on my feathers like the other
ducks like how this river must have been
activated recently the other ducks like
yeah I was probably barb she's really
good river activator well she's the only
River activator right now her son still
learned how to do it he's on ponds right
now it's gonna work his way up to full
river sometimes I tease her too I called
her I was like what are you doing she
goes I'm in Montana I just activated a
river I was like I already activated
that one you just double activated that
River
we should call Montana let them know
but my parents my parents have always
been into like nature and camping like
my dad took me whitewater rafting when I
was nine when I was nine do you see this
in front of you is this screaming
whitewater after two everybody like I
weigh about 125 pounds right now
can you picture me I was nine I weighed
38 pounds weight 38 pounds bigger
glasses no eyebrows my dad walked to the
house looked at that it was like that
kids ready to hit some whitewater rapids
but I was not ready I flew out of the
boat yeah that's that's what happens
when you're that little you're on an
inflatable raft and it bumps into a rock
it just launches you've got six feet
into the water it a throw a rope pulley
back in like you okay Tommy
you having fun I was like no not really
my cardigan is all wet and I should be
at home playing clarinet right now
I really don't know what I'm doing this
river this river has been activated you
know Davis is this hey your kale chips
are all wet
[Applause]
chuja beer I'm so excited this is fun
I've been having a good year I did have
I had a big break I was a semifinalist
on Last Comic Standing I was my big
break made it all the way to the
semifinals so my buddies made fun of me
they were like Tommy why didn't you make
it past the semi-finals
what happened why don't you make it
further than the semi-finals I was like
well I'm originally from Minnesota I
watched a lot of Minnesota sports so I
thought the semifinals was as far as you
could go
I thought I won Last Comic Standing for
a long time
called my mom I was like start buying
some houses someone made it to the
semi-finals yeah this year has been fun
last winter was kind of a bummer I I
broke my collarbone last winter that was
a bummer a couple days before Christmas
a broken I was doing something pretty
dangerous lob people have heard
themselves doing it I was doing house
carrying groceries I had two bags there
pretty heavy and somebody I put ice all
over my driveway for some reason not
sure who did it it shows up every year
but an ice is hard to see if you're not
looking for it you can walk right by
Ryan yeah I wish it came in colors
that'd be awesome like all red ice is
back yeah they had black ice but that's
clear too so I don't know why they call
it that it's confusing so I didn't see
it was walking like groceries I lost
both my feet I flew up I landed right on
my shoulder and right when it hit I was
like oh that feels different than ever
felt before I get hurt so bad and then
my body just started making pain sounds
that's never made before started coming
out of me and I thought I would have a
manly paint noise is what I always is to
like you seem like you would have a
manly paint sound like you'd be like
Ernie your beard would grow a little bit
more
oh that's an itch I'll walk myself to
the hospital it's cool but my pain noise
went up like it was just like just
laying in the driveway
surrounded by groceries so I could
survive a couple days nobody found me
let's leave my wife heard me she came
running out threw me into the car drove
me the hospital all the doctors came out
they're like who's your wife and labor I
was like that was me I made those sounds
I think there's a baby in my shoulder
feels like twigs then they brought me
into the emergency room and it was
winter so I had a bunch of layers on so
the doctor was like taking off my coat
and cardigan stuff and he got me down to
just a white t-shirt like my undershirt
and you go sir is it okay if I cut your
shirt off
I was like yeah you're gonna have to cuz
I can't lift my arm up to get off he
goes if I cut the shirt off it is gonna
ruin the shirt I was like no way for
real like what you're a medical school a
teacher that one just make sure the
patient knows when you take a scissor to
the shirt it's not gonna work the same
way as it did before you may want to get
some buttons in the gift shop on the way
out I told him I was like you can cut it
off I'm not too attached to this one
comes in bags of 12 so I should be able
to
I spill a tracking on the window I know
a guy so he cut the shirt off he sent me
to the x-ray machine and I came back
from the x-ray and he goes all Tom we
got bad news because your clavicles
broken and I stared at him for a while
cuz I'm a head shoulders knees and toes
I I don't really know what a clavicle is
I was like you probably just take it out
I guess I don't think I'm using my
clavicle for years he was like sir
that's your collarbone I was like oh
I've heard of that don't take that out I
want to keep that so then I asked him I
go so what's the next step like how do
we fix it
I was like do we go to surgery like what
did we do and he just pulled a sling out
he's like you're aware that for about
six to eight weeks I was like that's it
just a sling I was like you're not even
gonna set the bone or anything it was no
we don't we don't do that for a
collarbones he's like we would if it was
come on audio or if you're professional
athlete don't let me do some surgery for
you and then I was like whoa wait a
second nobody asked me if I was a
professional athlete when I got here I
didn't throw a survey or anything
I feel like you're making a judgment
call on this one like I walked in here
look at me like I don't think he's
throwing touchdowns this weekend
let's give him the sling but he was
right and it worked the sling it got
better
it worked and I got the bill the medical
bill I was come and we had a deductible
so we just paid paid that it was $900 is
what I paid so I think I paid $900 to
have a guy cut my shirt off I think
that's what happened yeah oh look I
looked at the itemized bills like $25
for the scissors 875 to cut the shirt
off my body and then the sling was free
the Aged threw it in there so that's a
good doctor I should have just called my
dad he would even like walk it off Tom
give me $50 aren't you quite your shirt
off and make that into a sling there you
go bud I'm kind of an awkward person
like it break my collarbone in awkward
way so I just operate on my life like
there's just awkward things about me
like I'm out of I I don't have eyebrows
they should be in by now all right good
man your third is how you're like you
put your glasses back on eyebrows are
important like you got great eyebrows
look at those way to go man
like I bet what you're surprised people
know you're surprised ha ha so jealous
cuz eyebrows are important like you need
them to express emotions now I got a
draw mine in but then I got to decide on
but I feel that whole day it's a big
commitment or hey I don't know I could
be surprised I guess it'll clear a
surprise well what if I'm angry though
then I want a good angry eyebrow maybe
I'll just do one surprised and one angry
I was turn my head accordingly to
whatever happens in the situation yeah
awkward awkward things always happened
to me too like a while ago I went
grocery shopping I got up early I was
all excited to get my grocery shopping
done
I had my basket I was walking in the
produce aisle and a sock just fell all
the bottom of my pants
sock just rolled out onto the floor I
kind of looked at like well how did I
get myself in this situation I think
what happened like I had done laundry
and there was an extra sock in there
just rolling her like hanging out and
then decided to come out but it's early
I'm so tired I didn't know what to do I
was like what should I put it in the
basket like that's gonna be a weird
awkward conversation at the register now
like sir you have a sock in here like
yeah you bet I do
did you want the other one that that one
hasn't fallen out yet so what I decided
to do was just set my basket down pick
up my sock and just leave the grocery
store I was like clearly they got going
to early today we got a great group get
her eyebrows on to try again focus
yeah I've had multiple awkward
experience at the grocery store to the
second is that an opera thing that
happened at the grocery store I got
yelled at by the grocery cart Corral guy
yeah yeah the grocery cart crowd is the
person that gets all the carts that are
out in the in the like the parking lot
like at a Target Walmart grocer and then
just brings a cart to the entryway I
didn't know they could yell you they can
yell at you and it was all a
miscommunication cuz I put my groceries
in my car and then when I when I put my
cart away I went by when I'm at those
kind of places I like to find a Corral
that's really far away and I'd like to
get some speed going I like to kind of
get run and then let it go and watch it
fly and bang around in the corral like
that's really exciting Tuesday for me
when I get to do that so I did I found
my Crowley executed the maneuver
perfectly but apparently there had been
the crowd guy was standing at a Corral
that was right next to my car
and he just thought he was waiting for
me patiently to put my groceries away
because he assumed I would just hand him
my cart like a normal human being but
instead he saw me just go dope and then
just push it like a mile away and then
I'm like right when I let go like I
realized something wrong cuz he was like
for real like I looked over like it was
like and I knew I could still solve the
problem cuz like a normal person would
just run grab the cart bring it back to
him Vic I'm sorry I was rude I didn't
see you but I just panicked was like oh
no it just got my car and drove away
so I'm pretty sure that guy hates me he
might have been the one that put ice on
my driveway I do like grocery shopping
though it's fun grocery shopping at my
grocery store though when everybody
comes in they always stop at that coupon
plate everybody has to go through the
coupon booklets it's really weird like
everyone walk I'm like can't we just we
all got to here can we just have the
deals like why do we have to do arts and
crafts for 20 minutes here flipping
through books like tearing them like ah
I tore the barcode I got it I can even
do a thing and sometimes I'll forget to
get the coupons I'll get all the way to
the register and they'll be like there's
a coupon for that over there I'm like
well the grocery Kurt corral guys over
there he's really mad at me can I go
back do you want this sock will you take
this sock it's a coupon I did play
clarinet I know that surprises a lot of
you a lot of people look at me like you
look more like a tuba man for sure I
play clarinet for a long time I never
really liked it like I wanted to play
saxophone but the band instructor was
like now you're more of a clarinet guy I
get you set up with a clarinet yeah it
was weird
like I don't want to hurt Amy's feelings
sir your big clarinet fan but I'd never
got into it like it sounds like a goose
to be honest like how do you serenade
somebody with that he's like this is
working did I break it this is what it's
supposed to sound like okay I did break
my clarinet Dostum a real rock star rock
star and I wasn't when I was little I
didn't just drop it I was about 15 years
old playing clarinet in my room and I
was like you know what would make this
clarinet song even cooler is some dance
moves that's what I thought I was like
let's step it up to the next level add a
little choreography so high just started
jumping around I was spinning in a
circle but apparently if you spend fast
enough the clarinets built in five
pieces so the bottom half will just kind
of fly off with smash against your wall
and then you do have to have a small
meeting with your parents because they
have some questions when there's just
shards of clarinet on their floor and I
didn't realize at the time that I
could've lied to him or we're not lied
but just left some details a hollow
story like when they're like son what
happened I would like I just dropped it
like normal kid yeah wasn't spinning
around I know that for sure yeah I
didn't see anybody's been in where I
could have been more clever like oh I
had a note that never existed and
exploded too good at music I told him
the truth I just like to head up I was
like I was I was doing some spicy dance
moves dance moves got way too spicy and
a clarinet smashed against the wall so
next time I'll just be a spicy further
away from the wall and that should solve
our problems they are mad I did I eat a
lot of kale chips that night so I got
excited news I'll be we married for five
years coming up and you have this summer
bleep I five-year wedding anniversary
yeah I did it
married I love being married like we
travel around and get to do exciting
stuff we got a dog recently which was it
so fun we got it we got a dog we got a
little Boston Terrier named olive we got
her from a breeder people were mad at us
like you should got a rescue dog why
don't you get a rescue dog and I
understand where they're coming from
like I think rescue animals are really
important but I've had rescue animals my
whole life like I was like I just want
one fresh one one time
and I just have one brand-new one that I
can mess up and somebody else can rescue
later
well technically it's still rescued Oh
it's my right now we would never give
all of us she's amazing when we were
driving her home my wife was like now we
got to get her outfits I was like what
she's like we have to get clothes for
the dog I was like I think you're
thinking of babies I'm pretty sure dog
can go a few days before he needs a
sweater because growing up I never
dressed up dog my dog's like they're all
naked they loved it not one of them ever
came up to be like my friend biscuit was
wearing a sweater today and all the
other dogs were talking to him so I want
to try that but it is fun to dress the
dog up though once you start it's a good
time like we get we got sweaters for
jackets like costume she's a Wonder
Woman costume dinosaur costume it's a
real practical stuff bumblebee costume
case you're having a picnic and there's
bees around you put the dog in the
bumblebee costume all the bees are like
oh that's a huge be stay away from that
it's great they make accessories to like
besides cold they make boots they make
winter boots for dogs yeah if you're
thinking about buying a winter boot for
your boots for your dog you may want to
pass I think it might be a scam cuz we
got the boots for our dog it took me 35
minutes to put four boots on my dog's
paws as I just wrestled with her and I
was like no these are good and then
which it was weird that that took that
long 35 minutes cuz it only took her
about 12 seconds to shoot am i four feet
right when she got outside like she just
crossed the doorway and they just shot
off was like and she looked at me like
what was this about I was like I don't
know you can eat him if you want
then we were going to my wife's cabin
and she was like we should get a life
jacket for the dog I was like a what
she's like a life jacket in case she
falls off the boat I like I'm pretty
sure there's a swim move named after
dogs I don't think they need life
jackets I think it's just built inside
them like they know how to do it
make the docq paddle like you just put
the dog in the water and if it doesn't
swim on the way home you get a new dog
the owners broken you got an upgrade to
the swimming kind that might have been a
cat you should double check and see if
thousand yeah but we got the lifejacket
I'm not a monster is hot-pink have a
handle on it so you just set the dog in
the water this bogged around and stared
at us just go out with the tide come
back a couple hours later just pick her
up my wife puts our dog on Instagram -
our dog has a lot of followers on
Instagram and I've never seen it before
so my wife will take a picture of the
dog and then she'll post a caption as if
the dog is talking so it's like I hope I
find some bacon today or like my ball
rolled under the couch hashtag mud is a
rough R uff like real good dog hammer
but then other people would respond and
they'll write captions but they write
them as their pets so it's just a bunch
of crazy people talking to each other
through their pets I was like this is
amazing we got another dog Harvey and I
was like I'm gonna run his Instagram but
I'm more literal I'm just like wolf wolf
girl Wolf Wolf Wolf cuz that that way I
know if it's real dogs that are
responding
we moved into a house recently and the
house is fun because the dogs can run
around the backyard we have more space
but if you own a house I didn't realize
that it comes with maintenance yeah did
you know that you have to fix stuff what
and I'm pretty handy like I have a tool
belt that is just a regular belt that I
duct-tape the screwdriver on a hammer -
I like to walk around the house well
it's cool and I fix some things like the
first thing that happened we had storms
in our neighborhood a lot of people's
trees fell down
none of our trees fell down but a whole
cable for our TV the cable just dropped
into the backyard and my wife was like
Tom can you take care of that I was like
you bet I can so I called the cable
company I was like hey this is Tommy her
smiling you know my cable fell down on
the ground I needed to go back up on
this guy where it was before and then
the guy on the head and he was kind of
confused he's like well actually the
computers tell me your cable is working
I was like oh yeah it is working it's
just on the ground though I normally
it's up in the air so I thought I'd call
you we'd get that tossed back up in the
air he kind of paused he's like now mr.
Ryman that computers is telling me it's
working I was like I know this is a
curveball this is a weird situation
right now yes okay it was working I
could watch TV but every time I go
outside to mow my lawn I got a little
cable up every time I make a pass
there's just more because I wanted to do
I was like is this the number I called
to put cables in this guy or is there a
different number that does that well you
could transfer me to or if you want to
kick this up to a supervisor I'm ready
if you are
I'm enjoying this conversation though
and then he was like well I'm in Seattle
and I was like
know what that has to do with anything I
was like did they just have their cables
on the ground in Seattle it's a new
thing they're doing people just drive
over them and stuff I was like you
aren't know where I am I'm in my
backyard turn to this cable that's on
the ground I really wanted to go back up
in the air I was like you want me to
unplug it real quick so it says it's not
working the butter bag in like all
unplug it you hit the button that sends
the person up I'll plug it back in come
on so then he was like fine we'll send
somebody out something this huge guy
shut up in my house is like six foot had
a big beard and he just put up like two
twisty ties and stared at me the whole
time it's like you couldn't figure this
out little guy
you can I found some rope or duct tape
from her belt there put him up here I
was like he didn't tell me about the
twisty tie trick I think he wants me to
move to Seattle so I got our
conversation but I did fix one thing
though I fixed our front step that was a
big day for me cuz we had some people
over for dinner and one of them stepped
through this step and I was like oh
that's not how those are supposed to
work normally if you're on a step you
want to be on top of it the whole time
you don't ever want to be inside of a
step if you are that one's gone bad
so no one got hurt luckily so I ripped
up the old plank and I ran to Home Depot
and I was like where's your step section
I need a new one and they brought me to
the lumberyard I've never seen so many
steps in my life at thousands I was like
I only need one today
it's good to know you guys have backups
so they cut it down to size for me and I
came home I screwed it in I'm still
proud of myself playing called my dad
right away I was like I just fix his
staff let's go whitewater rafting I'm
ready let's do it
I'll bring the kale chips yeah that's
fun my way I the with the other thing we
tried this summer we tried gardening for
the first time any gardeners as crowd
big gardeners here yeah yeah there's a
rowdy bunch gardeners what do you like
to garden what do you like to garden
kale doors that way you can let yourself
out we can edit you right out of this
special do you really grow kale nice
what's good I'm sure
send it to my dad he'll buy it from me
he needs a good suppliers in set
something off after their show that's
great
so do you grow other vegetables too as
well so like like tomatoes or tomatoes
carrots beets oh you're gonna have a
great salad in three to four months or
whatever yeah it is fun to garden though
is it it's a good you could watch
something grow like I tried we try to
grow a pepper plant that's what we were
gone where I was at the farmers market
they had one that was halfway done so
it's all I can't screw this up too bad
and I came home I brought the plant home
I set it on the deck I was watering it
every day and exciting it's exciting
because you're watching this this thing
grow and I was like at the end of the
season I'm gonna eat the pepper and
that's gonna be a big day for me and one
day I was in my living room just staring
out got to the at the deck at the pepper
plant and out of nowhere a squirrel just
ran up yeah everything went into like
slow-motion I was like what's happening
what's going on and he just like walked
up the back steps I swear he looked in
the eyes grabbed the pepper bit it and
it just ran off and my wife was sitting
there she's like I think that squirrel
just stole your pepper
and then my but I was devastated and my
buddy was like well why don't you put
some chicken wire around the plant and I
was like were you not even listening to
this story it was a squirrel there's no
chickens at all so that guy has no idea
what he's talking about but that's what
I learned like I'll never be able to
live off the grid like it's not gonna
work like you sound like you could be
really self-sustaining you have beets
and kale all day but if the zombie
apocalypse happens for me it's not gonna
be good what happened to Tommy like all
he was dead within two days they're
zombies Gabe knows the squirrels
squirrels ate his pepper my wife and I
we've been tweeting traveling recently -
we got to go whale watching that was so
exciting yeah if you ever get a chance
to go go whale watching is amazing this
is what you do you pay $50 you go on a
boat for about three hours and then you
don't see any whales
that's an amazing business plan that'd
be like if you came to the show tonight
paid your money and then like well the
comedians are wandering around town good
luck you find one he might tell you a
joke it'll be good oh yeah side note you
might get really sick while it's
happening
- there's people I paid that money got
seasick I felt so bad like they had
their head down the whole time so I just
described amazing whales to him I was
like there are so many whales it's like
50 well don't put your head up it's so
awesome AZ so worth of fifty dollars the
other trip my wife and I we went to New
Orleans New Orleans and there we got one
on a river ride to see alligators like
that and they throw food in to get the
alligators to come which is exciting but
what they were thrown in the water was
marshmallows and hot dogs that's what
they threw I got up so I was like why
are you feeding what Boy Scout see this
seems dangerous
you're gonna lose a troupe next week and
keep feeding marshmallows and hot it's
amazing though to see if you ever seen a
wild majestic animal PETA marshmallow
it's a really exciting and then
depressing at the same time I love being
married though it's exciting I am
proposing to my wife was the most
nerve-wracking thing I ever did oh yeah
who's married here clubs are married any
married people that's great
have you been married almost a year yeah
way to go you're doing it that's
fantastic where did you two meet you're
Provo that's great this is a great place
to meet people I've been around town for
the day so I was like this would be a
wonderful place to meet a significant
other so you're lucky how did you
propose that's what I was nervous about
you went to a restaurant Oh sounds
amazing was it and then did you did you
have did you like hide the ring in the
food or you think no that's right
dangerous you shouldn't do that
that's what were you surprised to be
proposed yes oh that's the best way and
you had the ring with you and everything
did you get down on one knee nice I
never know why we have to do that though
I feel like I feel like the first person
that ever proposed was like walking and
then drop the ring was like whoa who's
taking it up and then they turn around
like it's the most romantic thing
anyone's ever done like oh no no
everyone has to do this forever
I hope they have good knees that's sweet
give them a round of applause they're
excited yeah I was nervous I asked my
parents for permission before not
permission but I just wanted to give him
a heads up that this was gonna be in
their life for a while I hope you like
Claire next you hear a lot of it but the
way I did propose to her we're at her
family's cabin we're on the beach the
dogs were in their lifejackets bobbing
around was really romantic and my wife
really loves games so I was like oh do
you want to play hangman and she's like
yeah I do so I did all the lines in the
sand for the phrase will you marry me
and then had her start guessing letters
and that's when I started getting super
nervous so I was like oh this is really
happening like I'm about to propose and
I couldn't back out because I couldn't
think of another phrase that would fit
I'm fully committed I got to do this now
so she guessed letter M and I put the M
for the word marry but I forgot to put
the M for the word me which that's an
important part of that phrase it really
clarifies who was doing the proposing
what's happening so she was trying to
figure it out she was getting a little
confused and she was guessing more
letters and then finally she was like
she's like will you marry me I was like
I guess so it's not really traditional
but whatever
did you bring the ring because I brought
a ring then I got down on me I
officially proposed she said yes she was
all excited and after it was all done
she took me aside she was like Tommy I
love you but I just want to let you know
that there are two R's in the word marry
there's no spell check on a beach that's
a topless
like she was like who's Mary I was like
on of who Marion's for honeymoon we we
drove around Lake Superior cuz a lot of
people were like that's just like Hawaii
why don't you drive around one of the
Great Lakes but it's not like Hawaii
there's a lot like driving around a big
lake that's a huge lake it was fun
though like we camped in stage at lodges
but there's a lot of driving I got
pulled over it's you accidentally pulled
over which I didn't know was possible
but I do things a little differently I
think I grew up by Duluth Minnesota and
we're driving and a state trooper came
right behind my car and he started
shouting at it huh over the loudspeaker
like he's just like like mumble in I I
turned to my wife I was like I think
we're getting pulled over I was like
maybe I've had budget cutbacks so they
don't use lights and sirens anymore and
apparently they just mumble at she tell
you pull over so I started pulling over
and as I was pulling over I realized
another state trooper had pulled
somebody else over so this guy was
coming for his backup cuz any star
yelling at me more he's like I'm not
pulling you over get on boy don't pull
over but I'd already pulled over so I
was like I'm kinda stressed out you
gotta give me a second this is an
intense situation he was like sir just
move your car please get out of the way
so I started to get back onto the
freeway and a car just flew by
he was like well don't pull into
oncoming traffic sir
you know what I'm gonna have you stay
there I was like now really and pulled
over I just pulled myself are is
fantastic maybe he'll let me fill the
ticket out to like self checkout I used
to do this all by myself I probably give
myself a warning that's why I feel like
I deserve in this situation so then he
came walking over the car he's like
what's wrong with you I was like aw it's
been a big day where do you want to
start like I can't spell marry right my
dogs weren't a life jacket in the
backseat trunk is filled with kale chips
he let me go he's like you're a goofball
get out of here so now I just never pull
over for cops no matter what even if
there's five or six of them I'm like not
falling for that again boys school bit
words yeah I love my wife though cuz we
get we get we like get along because we
think of things the same way like we
have it way queer we had to move a
dresser we had to move this big
150-pound dresser from her upstairs to
our downstairs and my wife is like we
should take our shoes and socks off so
our feet grip better and I was like oh
yeah that makes sense
because you always hear about those
moving companies that are like barefoot
moving company shoes and socks top when
you're gonna be moving heavy furniture
around so we're both excited getting our
shoes and socks off and she was right
your feet droop grip better she's
correct but they don't grip as well when
the dresser slams down oh yeah but we
learned together as a team so it's fun I
learned new things about her all the
time - like she talks in her sleep that
was exciting I learned that at 10:30 in
the morning
yeah like I was laying there and all Sun
she just shot out of bed and was just
like watch out for the guy I was like
what she's right back to dreamer like
I'm out I was like I'm gonna need more
details on the guy apparently the
bedroom sometimes she just laughs in her
sleep too which is exciting still you
talk she has a beautiful laugh that's
one way as a stand-up comedian it was a
great it's wonderful but when it comes
out at 3:30 in the morning is terrifying
what are you laughing at is the guy back
what's happening let's get the dresser
we've been talking about having kids cuz
we have so much dog clothes I could put
that on a human we know when we first
moved in together my wife and I she
wanted to rack for a pet I didn't know
people had those for pets I thought they
just lived in sewers and stuff but I
love my wife so I was like if you want a
rat well go get one so we went to the
Humane Society and we bought a rack no
here's some advice if you ever do any
rat purchasing in your future definitely
go new on the rat
don't go rescue on the rat paybacks for
$3 a give brand new rat cuz we bought a
used elderly senior citizen rat and rats
only lived two to three years anyways
that they're healthy so this guy lived
about three months and he died he died
in my wife's hands like she was in the
living room I was in the kitchen making
a grilled cheese having a time of my
life then went from the other room I
heard deep sadness I had never heard
before like real guttural just like and
I was like if she playing clarinet with
Albie like
well I gotta go Jam so so I came I came
running in and she just had her patter
hand I felt really bad cuz that's her
buddy and her friend but at the same
time I was like we need to get that dead
rat out of her hands as soon as possible
because I'm pretty sure that's what took
Europe out I read about her in history I
probably shouldn't have it on our living
room so so he put it in a shoebox and we
we set it on our deck and I was like
what do you want it what do you want to
do with the rat and she was like I want
to bury it but it was February in
Minnesota so that did not work out very
well so I was like what are other
options and she was like maybe we could
cremate it I was like I just finished a
grilled cheese I've never done something
like that before she was like no
professionally I was like oh yeah we
should pay somebody that makes sense
skill should get some experts and we
looked into it and there were places
that would cremate the rat but this is
gonna cost $100 to cremate the rat which
exceeded our rack cremation budget by
$100 so then we had the rat on her deck
for a couple days which was like a
visitation for the neighborhood animals
to say their goodbyes and my wife came
home and was like Tommy we got to figure
out we're gonna do it this guy so what
we decided to do was just drive around
town till we found the most beautiful
spot that had a garbage can and we said
some words and we laid Lux with her to
rest our knee some nice and newspapers
he was by a really pretty lake my mom
came to activate it
thank you so much wonderful
[Applause]